Register of the Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary Sound Recordings, 1967-1980
Hoover Institution Archives
- Program list of Viewpoint and Ronald Reagan Radio Commentary, 1975-1979
  - Oil and the Shah of Iran, Program 75-15, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cuba, O.A.S., and Us, Program 75-15, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Helsinki Document, Program 75-15, 1 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - CIA Commission, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Letter to Congress, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Permits to Plow, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Ruritania, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Gun Control, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
    Guest: Patrick J. Buchanan
  - Mr. Nader's Great Treasury Raid, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Images, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Indians' Plight, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Crime Care and Prevention, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pollution #1, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pollution #2, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Pollution #3, Program 75-16, 5 August 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Washington Ironies, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Limitation, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Update: School Vandalism, UNICEF, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Saving Energy and Lives on the Freeway, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Reducing the Federal Burden, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Academic Freedom, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Strengthening Social Security I, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Strengthening Social Security II, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Strengthening Social Security III, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Regional Government, Program 75-17, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Few Ironies, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Economic Planning, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Public Employee Strikes, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Hudson Institute on Education, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Federal Registry I, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - More on Regulations II, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - New York, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Federal Rathole, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Nuclear Power, Program 75-18, 1 September 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Cedu Foundation, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - "Double-Dipping," Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Castro, Cleaver and Puerto Rico, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - "Peoples' Bicentennial Commission Survey," Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Can You Persuade a Leftist?, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Producers in the Minority, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Uncle Sam the Advertiser, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - U.S.P.S.'s Kokomo Plan, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Gun Laws, Drug Laws, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Communist Conspiracy? #1, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Communist Conspiracy? #2, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Communist Conspiracy? #3, Program 75-19, 1 October 1975 (Box 8)
  - Economic Planning, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Russian Wheat Deal, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Secret Service, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Détente, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Some Thoughts on Unemployment, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Samizdat, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Common Situs Picketing, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - New Gasoline Lines?, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Superintendent's Dilemma, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Incredible Bread Machine, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - A Break for the Handicapped, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
    Guest: Julie Nixon Eisenhower
  - Welfare Abuses, Program 75-20, 1 October 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Clear cutting, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Government Pay, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Letter to Employees, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Panama Canal, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Welfare Letter, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Land Use Policy #1, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Land Use Policy #2, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - National Land Use Policy #3, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Trouble with New York City, Program 75-21, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Crime, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - What Would You Do if You Woke to Find a Burglar in Your Home, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
    Guest: William F. Buckley
  - Is Gerald Ford Ganging Up on New York City?, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Should Ex-CIA Employees Be Treated as Second-Class Citizens?, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Hoe Do You Talk Back to Eric Sevaried?, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Should We Really Give Away the Panama Canal?, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Women in Government and Politics #1, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Women in Government and Politics #2, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Women in Government and Politics #3, Program 75-22, 1 November 1975 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Convention #1, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Platforms A, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Platforms B, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Platforms C, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Panama Canal, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Getting Back at the Bureaucrats A, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - [Getting Back at the] Bureaucrats B, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Congress' Automatic Pay Raise, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Women's March, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - China, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Shaping the World for 100 Years to Come, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Tax Reform, Program 76-01, 1 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Median in the Message, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Panama's Press, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Mao's China, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - About the Press, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Education (A), Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Education (B), Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Herman Kahn, Futurist, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Paperwork and Bureaucrats, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Institute for Contemporary Studies, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Humphrey-Hawkins Bill (Jobs A), Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Humphrey-Hawkins Bill (Jobs B), Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - FORBES on "full" Employment, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - President Coolidge, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - Nuclear Wastes, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Hope of Mankind, Program 76-02, 21 September 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Ford Strike, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Election Day, November 2, 1976, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Vietnam, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Reporters, Sources, and Laws, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Fate of 14 (b), Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Speedy Trial Act, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Welfare, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Running Fence, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - "Bread Machine" and Janeway, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Soviet TV and America, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Government Forms, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Milton Friedman #1, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Milton Friedman #2, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Sweden 1, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Sweden 2, Program 76-03, 18 October 1976 (Box 8)
  - Diamond Lanes, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Tax Reform I, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Tax Reform II, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Hoover's America Plan, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Africa, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Freedom Train, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Katyn Forest, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Big Government and the Cities, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - San Francisco, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Berkeley's Street Tax, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Politics of the Federal Government, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Alaska Gas Pipeline, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Communes, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - New Directions, Program 76-04, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Centralized Planning, Program 76-05, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Bureaucrats Revisited, Program 76-05, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Inflation and the Property Tax I, Program 76-05, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Inflation and the Property Tax II, Program 76-05, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Land Use Planning, Program 76-05, 2 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Education I, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Education II, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Campaign Reminiscence, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Citizen's Choice, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Liberals, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Red Hen, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Government Cost I, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Government Cost II, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Solar Energy, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Britain, Program 76-05, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Unemployment and Inflation I, Program 76-06, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Unemployment and Inflation II, Program 76-06, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Unemployment and Inflation III, Program 76-06, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Unemployment and Inflation IV, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Unemployment and Inflation V, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Cuba, Program 76-06, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Terrorism, Program 76-06, 16 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - U.N., Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Vietnam I, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Vietnam II, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Pardons, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Child Services Act, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Socialism, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Soviet Visas, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Human Rights Double Standard, Program 76-06, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Postal Profits, Program 76-07, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Special Parents; Special Kids, Program 76-07, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Update on Social Security, Program 76-07, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Crime I, Program 76-07, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - Crime II, Program 76-07, 30 November 1976 (Box 8)
  - America's Strength, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Crime [and Poverty], Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Public Broadcasting, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Welfare, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Tricentennial, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - The Family and Other Living Things, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Milton Friedman and Chile, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - South Vietnamese Boat People, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - New Hampshire and Vermont, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Memo to a Liberal, Program 76-07, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Planned Economy, Program 76-?, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Strategic Stockpiles, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Farewell Speeches, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Campaign Law Violated?, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Television, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Korea, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - People Power, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Tax Limit, Program 76-08, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Televisions and Profits, Program 76-08, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Health Care, Program 76-08, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Rapid Transit, Program 76-08, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Junk Food, Program 76-08, 22 December 1976 (Box 8)
  - Building Codes, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - OSHA, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - More About OHSA, Program 76-08, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - The Real China?, Program 76-09, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Capital Gains, Program 76-09, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - More About Taxes, Program 76-09, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Postcard Registration, Program 76-09, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Poverty, Program 76-09, 19 January 1977 (Box 8)
  - Amnesty, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Foundations, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Conservation, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - China, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Tom Wolfe's New Book, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Torrijos, Human Rights and Money Lenders, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - IBM, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Congress, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Civil Service, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Rhodesia, Program 76-09, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Minimum Wage, Program 76-10, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Taxes I, Program 76-10, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Taxes II, Program 76-10, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Taxes III, Program 76-10, 2 February 1977 (Box 8)
  - Agriculture Day, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Update on Cuba, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cuba II, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - England, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Seabrook, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Germany, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Added Inflation, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Census, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Sports and Religion, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Amtrak, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Free Press and Property Rights, Program 76-10, 2 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Economic Plan, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Equal Rights Amendment, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Taxes, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Intelligence, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Saccharin, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Review, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Chile I, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Chile II, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Chile III, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Labor, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Murphy's Law, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Day Care Centers, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Charity, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - "Argo Merchant," Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Government By the People, Program 76-11, 23 March 1977 (Box 8)
  - Redwoods, Program 76-11, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Capital Punishment, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Electoral College, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Brezhnev, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Gasohol, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Coal Tar, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Human Rights, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Jamaica, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Recycled Theater, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Environment, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Education and Religion, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Miranda, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Student Letter, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - Arson, Program 76-12, 13 April 1977 (Box 8)
  - FBI, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - A Renewable Source, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Rhodesia, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Lawnmowers, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cuba and Africa, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Kidco, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Ken Piao, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Punishment, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Drugs and the FDA, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Lord Chalfont, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Recycled Streamliner, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Strategy I, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Strategy II, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Bill Niehouse, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Postcard Registration, Program 76-13, 4 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Korea, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - FBI, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Voting, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Public Servants, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cuba - Trouble in Paradise, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - National Review, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cambodia I, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cambodia II, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cambodia III, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Soviet Workers, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Who Government Costs Money, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Marijuana, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Government Spending, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Inflation, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Russians, Program 76-14, 25 May 1977 (Box 8)
  - Privacy Bureau, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Vietnam, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Oil I, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Oil II, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cuba, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Episcopal Controversy, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Intelligence, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - OSHA, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - DNA research, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Indexing, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Force Account Work, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Common Sense Bureaucrats, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Economic Fairy Tapes, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Health Costs, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Names, Program 76-15, 15 June 1977 (Box 8)
  - Private Property, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - The Hatch Act, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - South Africa, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Food Stamps, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Man's Castle, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Jamaica, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Endangered Medicine, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Socialized Medicine, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - The Principal's Principles, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Property Rights, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cambodia, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Bulletins, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Spending, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Government Cost, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Quiz, Program 76-16, 6 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Food Stamps, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Neutron Bomb I, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Neutron Bomb II, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Ukraine, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Tax Shift, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Drunk Driving, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Korea I, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Korea II, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Korea III, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Laxalt, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Human Rights, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Snail Darter, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Busing, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - NEA, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Porpoises and Tuna, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Small Business, Program 76-17, 1 July 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cover Up, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Justice Department, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Unemployment, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Medical Care, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - World Research, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - TRIS, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Montage, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Dream World, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Tom Hayden, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Business, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Inflation, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Korea, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Rhodesia, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - Foreign Aid, Program 76-18, 15 August 1977 (Box 8)
  - L.A. Times [Panama Canal], Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama Canal I, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama Canal II, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - The Bible, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Kettering, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Government Costs, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cuba I, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Cuba II, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Youth Employment, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - The Olympics, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Government Can Cost Less I, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Government Can Cost Less II, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Pensions, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Blackout, Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Furbish Lousewart [Lousewort], Program 76-19, 6 September 1977 (Box 8)
  - Pot, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Rhodesia, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Carter Welfare Reform #1, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Carter Welfare Reform #2, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Stalinoids, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Hospital Costs, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Mozambique, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Olympics, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Tax Limitation, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Air Bags, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Camps, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Military, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Property Rights [California Redwoods Parks], Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Congressional Committees, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - The Myth of the Medicare Millionaires, Program 77-20, 27 September 1977 (Box 8, Box 2)
  - Energy, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Carter Welfare Reform, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Treaties, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama I, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama II, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Panama III, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Steel, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Land, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Taxes, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Energy I, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Energy II, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)
  - Equal Time, Program 77-21, 18 October 1977 (Box 8)